whodoyou.com 2018-10-09

# Privacy policy: WhoDoYou – Local businesses recommended on social media

Your privacy is important to WhoDoYou. We hope this privacy policy will help you understand how WhoDoYou collects, uses and safeguards the personal information you provide to us on our site.

The WhoDoYou Privacy Policy (the "Privacy Policy") applies to your use of the Service, including the [www.whodoyou.com](https://www.whodoyou.com/www.whodoyou.com) website, the Facebook Canvas Page and other sites and pages under the whodoyou.com domain (collectively, the "Site"). By accessing or in any way using the Site or the Service, you agree to the practices described in the Privacy Policy, whether or not you are a registered user.

Please note that this Privacy Policy does not apply to any third party sites that you may access via the Site (for example, by clicking on a link), or to any relationships you may have with the businesses listed on the Site.

We welcome any feedback or questions at: [privacy@whodoyou.com](mailto:privacy@whodoyou.com). 

## Collection of Information

When you visit the Site and Login with your Facebook account, you provide us with two types of information:

 **Your Facebook identification.** You knowingly choose to disclose this by accepting the Facebook permissions dialog to help take advantage of the full range of services and information offered on the Site, which also may include personal information such as your name, profile photo, current city, groups, statuses, your friends statuses, friends on Facebook and email address.

 **When you browse or use our Service.** We may collect information about your use of the Site as detailed in the below section.

## What information we collect and how we use it

 **Personal Information**

For both Personal and Service Provider Accounts: We may use your email address to send you notifications, WhoDoYou newsletters, other updates, and to contact you both ourselves, and on behalf of other users (such as other users who send you messages or respond to a question you posted.) If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided on every email communication. We use the email address that you set in your contact info on Facebook. To change this at anytime please click on the update info tab on your Facebook profile and edit your contact info.

We use your current location as recorded in Facebook to calculate and display the distance that a local service provider's range of service is from your location and to provide you with public recommendations from others in your neighborhood according to your current location.

When you log in with Facebook, we use your social graph from Facebook to differentiate and sort results - we always show you first, reviews written by your Facebook friends, and after that, reviews written by other users, followed by Facebook posts, i.e. recommendations.

When you log in with Facebook we search posts and comments from your friends and groups and attempt to identify posts related to local business recommendations. Any recommendations located within your network and not tagged explicitly as public will stay within your network. we'll never share this private information.

For Service Providers only: We may use your email address and phone numbers to send you notifications and updates both ourselves, and on behalf of other users (such as other users who send you text or voice messages) and for activity relating to your Provider Account (such as when users review or recommend your business or when a user posts a question related to your service expertise). We may use your business phone and mobile phone numbers to notify you of activity on your profile page, and/or to deliver a message to such effect via a phone call, text or voice messages. We may also use your mobile phone number to notify and, in some cases, deliver to you via SMS, text or voice messages sent to you by other users. We use your business address to: (a) calculate and display the distance your business location is from the location of users; and (b) display a map of the location of your business. We may use your phone number to call you to verify that you are the owner or authorized representative of a business.

You may choose not to receive e-mail (and for Service Provider Accounts, SMS text messages and phone calls) of these types by emailing us at providers@whodoyou.com.

 **Provider profile data.** Provider profile data is entered into our system primarily by end users, but occasionally we merge listings from other partners or sites. At this time, you cannot edit your profile information directly unless you claim your listing, and pay the monthly or annual provider fee. This is to ensure information is not improperly modified or unintentionally changed.

 **Login Information.** By logging in to WhoDoYou, you choose to connect through your Facebook account through Facebook Connect so that: (a) WhoDoYou can personalize your site experience by highlighting your Facebook friends and their reviews and recommendations (b) publish your WhoDoYou activity on your Facebook news feed (for example, notification when you post a new review or ask for advice) and (c) so we can search through posts and comments related to local businesses to show you recommendations by category from your Facebook friends and groups. When you connect with your Facebook account, Facebook provides WhoDoYou with the information that you agree to share with the WhoDoYou application. This includes basic information about yourself, such as name and email. In addition, you give permission to the WhoDoYou app to access your location and locations of your friends as well as access to your posts and your friends posts. Relevant information is stored in the WhoDoYou database.

Currently, the only way to log in to WhoDoYou is with your Facebook account. We reserve the right to change the login procedure, but we will alert you that changes have been made.

 **Submissions.** We store and may publicly display your submissions in order to help provide the Service. When we display your submissions, we do so together with your account name. The term "account name" means: (a) for Personal Accounts, your name as published on Facebook; and (b) for Provider Accounts, your first name and last name, or your business name. The term "submissions" refers to the information that you submit or post to the Site for public display, such as business ratings, reviews, photos, complaints, comments and responses to reviews. Submissions will be visible to all WhoDoYou users. The information that you display as part of your account profile on WhoDoYou is taken from the information you use on your Facebook account. If you conduct a Facebook action on WhoDoYou this may be shown within your network of friends, depending on your privacy settings in Facebook.

 **Feedback.** If you contact us to provide feedback, register a complaint, or ask a question, we will record any personal information and other content that you provide in your communication so that we can effectively respond to your communication.

 **Surveys or Contests.** From time-to-time, we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests, sweepstakes or surveys on the Site. If you participate, we will request certain personal information from you. Participation in these contests, sweepstakes or surveys is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes standard Facebook login information. We use this information to notify contest winners and award prizes, to monitor Site traffic or personalize the Site (in the case of anonymous information collected in surveys) and to send participants an email newsletter. We may use third party service providers to conduct these surveys or contests. If we do use third parties, we will implement reasonable contractual and technical protections limiting the use of that information to the WhoDoYou-specified purposes. We will not share the personal information you provide through a contest or survey with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice.

 **Activity.** We may record information relating to your use of the Site, such as the searches you undertake, the pages you view, your browser type, IP address, requested URL, referring URL, and timestamp information. We use this type of information to help us administer the Site and provide Service to you. We also use this information in the aggregate (on an anonymized basis) to perform statistical analyses of user behavior and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the Site. We may share the results of this analysis (on an aggregated, anonymized basis) with third parties to help us provide or expand the Site or the Service. 

**Cookies.** We send cookies to your computer in order to uniquely identify your browser and improve the quality of our service. The term "cookies" refers to small pieces of information that a website sends to your computer's hard drive while you are viewing the Site. We may use both session cookies (which expire once you close your browser) and persistent cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them or they expire in accordance with their own terms). Persistent cookies can be removed by following your browser help file directions. If you choose to disable cookies, some areas of the Site may not work properly or at all.

 **Enforcement.** We may use the information we collect in connection with your use of the Site (including your personal information) in order to investigate, enforce, and apply this Privacy Policy.

 **Data Processing.** By using WhoDoYou, you are consenting to have your personal data transferred to and processed in Israel and in the United States.

 _Children Under Age 13._ WhoDoYou does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 years or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 13 years of age, please do not attempt to register for WhoDoYou or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number,or email address. No one under 13 years of age may provide any personal information to or on WhoDoYou. If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under 13 years of age without verification of parental consent, then we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13 years, please contact us at feedback@whodoyou.com.

 _Children Between the Ages of 13 and 18._ While we intend that only users who are of legal age to form a binding contract (typically 18 years old) use the Site, we recommend that minors over the age of 13 years ask their parents for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet.

 **Transfer of Information**

We may distribute your User Content to third parties to help promote or benefit the Site or the Service. The third parties may in turn publicly display or publish your submissions in connection with their own websites, media platforms and products or services. When we distribute your submissions to third parties, we typically include your account name (but not your personal information unless you include your personal information in your submissions).

We may provide information to service providers to help us bring you the services we offer. Specifically, we may use third parties to facilitate our business, such as to host the Site at a co-location facility for servers, to send out email updates about WhoDoYou, to remove repetitive information from our user lists, to provide messaging systems, to process payments for products or services, to conduct quality assurance testing, facilitate creation of accounts, provide technical and customer support, or provide specific services, such as synchronization of your contacts with other software applications. Where we utilize third parties for the processing of any personal information, we implement reasonable contractual and technical protections limiting the use of that information to the WhoDoYou-specified purposes.

We may share your personal information with our current or future affiliated companies, in which case we will require them to honor this Privacy Policy. If the ownership of all or substantially all of the WhoDoYou business, or individual business units owned by WhoDoYou, Inc., were to change, then your user information may be transferred to the new owner so the service can continue operations. In any such transfer of information, your User Content and other information would remain subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy.

We may be required to disclose user information pursuant to lawful requests, such as subpoenas or court orders, or in compliance with applicable laws. We do not reveal information until we have a good faith belief that an information request by law enforcement or private litigants meets applicable legal standards. Additionally, we may share account or other information when we believe it is necessary to comply with law, to protect our interests or property, to prevent fraud or other illegal activity perpetrated through the Service or using the WhoDoYou name, or to prevent imminent bodily harm. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, agents or government agencies.

We may disclose information in the aggregate to third parties relating to user behavior in connection with actual or prospective business relationships with those third parties, such as content distributors. For example, we may disclose the number of users that have been exposed to, or clicked on, provider profiles.

## Links

The Site may contain links to other web sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites. We encourage our users to read the privacy policies of other sites they visit when they leave the Site. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by WhoDoYou.

## Opt out options and controlling your personal data

From time to time, WhoDoYou may send you email communications and marketing newsletters. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided or email feedback@whodoyou.com and we'll remove you from our mailing lists. 

If you don't want your posts to appear on WhoDoYou you may email feedback@whodoyou.com and WhoDoYou will make reasonable efforts to fulfill your request within a reasonable period of time. Additionally, to prevent future public posts from appearing on WhoDoYou you can change your privacy settings from the account settings tab on Facebook so they're not selected for public viewing. Posts that have been selected for public viewing means that people who are not your Facebook friends, nor in any of your groups, can see your posts, consistent with Facebook's policies and terms of service. 

To the extent you include personal information in your submissions (such as a comment about your project or details about your interactions), third parties may be able to identify you, associate you with your user account, and contact you. For service providers, third parties can also associate you with your user account using the search feature on the Site, but only if the third party already knows your business name. **Please do not include information in your submissions that you expect to keep private.**

If you wish to remove the permissions you granted WhoDoYou, you can do so by accessing your Facebook application settingsand removing WhoDoYou. If you wish to delete your account information stored on WhoDoYou, contact us at feedback@whodoyou.com. Service providers may also choose to remove a premium business profile from display on the Site (this will result in the business details being removed from display on the Site) by contacting WhoDoYou directly at feedback@whodoyou.com. After your account is closed, your personal information that you provided when registering for the Site may persist in backup copies for a reasonable period of time, but will not be generally available to users of the Site. Note that other User Content posted to the Site, such as reviews, recommendations, complaints, feedback, comments, questions and answers, will generally continue to be displayed on the Site.

## Security

WhoDoYou takes appropriate precautions to protect our users' information. Your account information is located on a secured server behind a firewall. Because email, instant messaging and SMS text messages are not recognized as secure communications, we request that you not send private information to us by email, instant messaging or SMS text message services. If you have any questions about the security of the Site, please contact us at feedback@whodoyou.com.

## How to contact us

If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, you can contact us by email at privacy@whodoyou.com

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

Your use of the Site, and any disputes arising from it, are subject to this Privacy Policy. WhoDoYou may occasionally revise this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in its Services. We reserve the right to change the provisions of this Privacy Policy at any time, but we will alert you that changes have been made by indicating on the Privacy Policy the date it was last updated. Your use of the Site following the posting of such changes or revised statement will constitute your acceptance of the changes.

Last modified: February 2015
